4upld.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - 4upld - File Sharing Made Simple

__

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. At 4upld, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit 4upld, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties and would never ever spam your mail box.   

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP in most of the case which is solely used to be able to assure that the service is running smoothly and also protect your personal information (For example we record your the number of the IP addresses used to login to your account and if it is more than a certain limit we would block your account till you open a support ticket, this is to assure that your account has not be compromised or shared in anyway)   

## Cookies

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site (Language) and also your login default. Your cookies are also used for advertisements, for example it could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to use some of our features, such as Texl. We also use third party advertisements on 4upld to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing the related ads to where you live to you) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).   

## Copyright

If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of an owner of the copyright or of any exclusive right under the copyright, and believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please report your notice of infringement to 4upld by providing all the necessary information (More detail can be found [here](http://4upld.com/dmca.html)). 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to send us a ticket and we would be happy to help you.
